Contact

shakhee95@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/baishakhee-mardi-733b3a175 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

web api Bluetooth

Mobile Application Development

BAISHAKHEE MARDI

Android Developer || Freelancer||

Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Android with Java ,kotlin and Flutter. Strong engineering professional with a BCA focused in Computer Application from Kolhan University, West Singhbhum Jharkhand.

Experience

Versatile Mobitech Pvt Ltd Android Developer November 2022 - Present (10 months)

Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Design and build advanced applications for the Android platform Collaborate with cross-functional teams to define, design, and ship new features

Work with outside data sources and APIs

Work on bug fixing and improving application performance

Continuously discover, evaluate, and implement new technologies to maximize development efficiency

Exceloid Soft Systems

Software Engineer

October 2019 - October 2022 (3 years 1 month)

Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Design and build advanced applications for the Android platform Collaborate with cross-functional teams to define, design, and ship new features

Work with outside data sources and APIs

Work on bug fixing and improving application performance

Continuously discover, evaluate, and implement new technologies to maximize development efficiency

Ekjut

Internet sathi

August 2017 - April 2018 (9 months)

Jharkhand, India

I used to teach village women how to use smartphones

Education

CHANDIGARH UNIVERSITY

Master of Computer Applications - MCA, Computer Science · (January 2022 - December 2023)

Kolhan University, West Singhbhum Jharkhand Bachelor of Computer Application - BCA, Computer Application · (2013 - 2017)